# Shubhankar Swain

I am student at MIT WPU

As MIT WPU's **Computer Science** student, Shubhankar Swain, my experience as a web developer, Head of Data, and Research Executive influences my dynamic academic approach. I've executed projects like an **Amazon clone**, showcasing practical expertise.

✓ shubhankarswain16@gmail.com

9004987482

Pune, India

in linkedin.com/in/shubhankar-swain-82697924b

github.com/SwippyA

# **EDUCATION**

# **Computer Science**

MIT WPU

08/2022 - Present Pune ,india

Computer Science

Bsc.Computer Science
 8.8 CGPA

# HSC board

Keraleeya Samajam Dombivlis Model College Near Police Colony Plot No 32 Phase II MIDC Residential Area Dombivli East Dist Thane 421 203

08/2021 - 07/2022 Kalyan ,thane 8.0 CGPA

#### SSC Board

Divine Paradise high school

07/2019 - 06/2022 kalyan,thane

Courses

8.9 CGPA

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Data Head

Innovation Hub

10/2022 - 04/2023 Pune 411038.India

**Skills:** Microsoft Excel Achievements/Tasks

 Directs comprehensive management and strategic utilization of organizational data.

#### Research Executive

### **Future Tech Global Solution**

06/2022 - 09/2022 Pune 411038

**Skills:** Microsoft Excel Achievements/Tasks

 Plans and executes research projects in line with organizational objectives.

 Conducts thorough analysis of research findings and provides meaningful interpretations.

# **SKILLS**

Web-Development

React .js

Javascript/Tailwind

C++ programming

Data Structure

C Programming

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

amazon-clone-Web

My Portfolio

Demo gym website

Todo-list-project

Data structure

## **CERTIFICATES**

Introduction to Programming Using Python

Machine learning

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Professional Working

Proficiency

Odisa

Full Professional Proficiency

Programming Languages
Full Professional Proficiency

C++/Javascript/C/pythan /html5/css

Full Professional Proficiency

# **INTERESTS**

Sketching

Movies

Anime

Excercise